## **BANUPRIYA**

### WEB DEVELOPER / SAP ASSISTANT



♣ Female

**C** 07721405918

banupriyacse0@gmail.com

0

https://github.com/BanuRK/masterchef.git

Peterlee, England

### **SKILLS**

Language

English, Telugu, Tamil

Computer

Word, Excel, Power point

Computer

HTML5, CSS, Java Script

Computer

SAP

### CERTIFICATIONS

2014: Sample certification's title

### INTERESTS

I like net surfing, music, online games

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

banupriyacseO@gmail.com 07721405918,Peterlee England

### **OBJECTIVE**

Four Years of Experience in handling SAP related activities and Creating, maintaining, reviewing Production departments documentation like SOP(Standard Operating Procedure), MBR (Manufacturing Batch Record), interested in using my extensive FULL STACK development skills at your organisation. I am interested in growing my skill set in an entry level position while contributing to your organisation's continued success.

### EDUCATION

P.S.R Rengasamy college of engineering for women's, Anna University

Computer science and engineering

May 2011 - June 2014

- - - Front End

### WORK EXPERIENCE

Bristol laboratories(pharmaceutical), England

Documentation reviewer /SAP activities

2022 - now

Data maintaining in SAP SYSTEM, Production Documents reviewing like MBR,SOP preparation and revising the MBR .preparation and updating staff's training records . In process checks for product(Tablets)etc.

Bristol laboratories(pharmaceutical), England

Documentation reviewer /SAP

activities

2020 - 2021

Data maintaining in SAP SYSTEM, Production Documents reviewing like MBR,SOP preparation and revising the MBR .preparation and updating staff's training records . In process checks for product(Tablets)etc.

UPMS

Teacher

banu 🗴

2015 - 2017

#### **ACTIVITIES**

Entri Elevate

Full Stack Development

2023 - now

learning Full Stack Development course

RASI EDUCATION SYSTEM

System administrator/Teacher

2009 - 2011

Conducting the class about basic of computers.